collector,
A rich tax
Jericho,
everyone in
hated by
at
just one look
wanted
Jesus.
to
short
He was too
crowd,
see over the
no
something
so he did
do.
man would ever
grown
a tree.
climbed
He
spot,
reached that
Jesus
When
stopped.
he
up.
looked
He
this man
called
And he
name:
by
Zacchaeus,
haste,
make
down;
and come
must
for to day I
at thy house.
abide
leaders.
religious
Not the
who thought
crowd
Not the
him more.
deserved
they
cheat,
A
tree.
up a
and said:
climbed down
Zacchaeus
Behold,
Lord,
goods
the half of my
to the poor;
give
I
taken
and if I have
from any man
thing
any
accusation,
by false
fourfold.
I restore him
he
changed what
conversation
One
money,
did with his
life,
his
name.
told him why:
Jesus
of man
Son
For the
to seek and
come
is
was
which
to save that
lost.
story.
Zacchaeus's
That's not just
for
came
Jesus
That's why
too.
you